Here we go... Upokami!
This time we have with us Moe Kamikuroryo of Andigumi
and Shin Maeda of Beyonz Amorigawa Bi.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsals, etc.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Kami Kuroyasu, was asked by Rin Hashizako on the Angelem radio
Rin Hashizako gave me a mission.
Rin Hashizako, I'm Rikako Sasaki, Rin Hashizako's senior member, and I'm Ayano Kawamura, Ayano Ise.
I'm Ayano Kawamura, and I'm Reira Ise, and each of us has a mission from Rin.
Rin gave us a mission.
My mission was to meet the Beyond members at their homes.
"Here we are, Mr. Takao." The mission was to take a video of us at home with the Beyond members.
I was at home with Maeda Shin-chan and Beyond's Maeda Shin-chan.
Here's the video we shot.
Mr. Takao
I shot a video called "Mr. Takao.
I couldn't do it alone, so I asked Ayano Kawamura to help me.
I asked her to join me when she went to Shin Kawamura's house.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, I did.
I took that video.
Yes.
Ayano Kawamura was there?
Yes, the three of us.
And then I was disqualified.
Achana
Yes, and Rikako Sasaki didn't complete the mission either.
So we climbed Takao together.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, we had to make sure we climbed Takao-san and take a video of us arriving at Takao-san.
Yes, that was the penalty.
I was unexpectedly disqualified, so I'm going to try my best to climb Mt.
Please do your best.
I would like to talk about the children who passed the audition for the 25th anniversary.
At the 3ofus concert, the new members introduced themselves.
Yes, they are.
Three very cute girls.
Yes.
Jump up and down
Yuuchan, Yuuchan, and Fuuchan.
So cute!
I call them "cute".
All three of them were really cute, and they would watch us rehearsing from the audience.
I waved to them and they waved back.
So cute!
We've added a lot of new members to our group, nine new girls, so I'm really looking forward to seeing them.
And a girl 10 years younger than me just joined.
What a surprise.
I'm so surprised.
Yes, I was.
I'm sure she'll be making more and more appearances on UpCami, so please look forward to it!
Let's start with up-cam this time!
Tsubaki Factory Stay Free & Stay Tune Instrumental Recording
Here is the guitar recording of Stay Free & Stay Tune from Tsubaki Factory's latest album!
Stay Tune audio
Ending
Thank you for watching!
I'll be attacked and beaten more
Yes, thank you.
The sound is already good, though.
Let me guess... another Telecas or something.
You want me to try?
Yes, for now.
Okay.
BGM
I think we've got it.
Here's the line.
We'll double-double it from here.
I think that's a good idea.
It's going to be a little bit different.
The second line is coming in.
The first one, on the other hand, looks a little masculine.
I understand.
That might be good.
Okay, I'll start with the first Les Paul.
I understand.
Okay, please.
Yes, please.
Music
Music. Music.
Music.
I'll be more aggressive
I'll go harder.
Yes, sir.
Let's see...
Telecasts are good after that, right?
Yes... if you give me two of these first.
Yes, sir.
And then I'll just get two bars of the...
Just two bars of the intro.
May I replay it?
Yes, of course.
Music.
Do you want to play the second one?
Yes, please.
Music
Let's get more aggressive.
In the path of A CMT
That map...
Where do you want to go?
I'm running away
To orsmm сер shadow piece in 2004
Cool kyber.
This commercial is
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much. Please make a guitar change.
I'd like to be more aggressive.
Thank you for watching.
by H.
I want to be more aggressive.
I'll be more aggressive.
Yes, I thought it was perfect. What do you think?
Yes, it's fine.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Now, while you're taking a short break, would you mind putting up the microphone?
Yes, I'll take a shot.
Okay, I'll take a shot. Let's do it.
Okay.
I'm not going to give up, but I'm going to keep going and you know what? What's up with that?
Do you want a double?
Yes, let's do it.
Let's put it on.
Let's go a little lower.
If you keep going without giving up, you'll see, you'll get a comb-over. What's up with that?
Isn't he very good at it?
Right?
Perfect.
One more thing, before the last chorus, the top of the last chorus?
The top of the last chorus.
You can hear this part, can't you?
Yes.
Wow! It sounds like "Wow!
Yes, that's right.
Would you like to try one?
Yes.
ое Poướci!
Cherie!
Oh my God!
Honestly.
C authoritarian!
JK 2000 startsayevening.
Focusing Hyung!
h Vibe
Laboratory
wooooooooo
Can we go a little bit further with the "Nigolas"?
wooooooo
mutation
ni
Park
wooooooo wooooooo mutation ni park
wooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
yeah
It's so good.
And the atmosphere, too.
Like this.
Okay, before that...
STAY FREE STAY TUNE
STAY FREE STAY TUNE STAY
STAY TUNE
STAY FREE
Okay, up.
stayfree staytully
Yes, sir.
Life-Life. Synthetic holdi...
I'll get the back of the house.
Stayfree, staytue, staytue.
Stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree stayfree
Stayfree Staytue
Stayfree Stayfree Stayfree
Okay, that's all.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, anyway, it's a straight gulp, isn't it?
Yes, I wonder, what's the hard part?
I didn't dare to do anything, I just played it simply and without hesitation!
I'm actually a super technician.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I said it myself.
No, that's not true.
But my order this time was to make it a little melo-punk, a little melo-core.
I was really into melocoa in high school.
I see.
I was very much of that generation, so I played it while remembering those days.
I mainly used this Les Paul guitar and a Telecaster.
and a Telecaster.
The Les Paul has a very strong sound, with a lot of expansion.
The Les Paul has a very powerful sound, and the Telecaster has a very broad sound, but the Telecaster is like a sword thrusting through the middle of the broad sound.
Well, I don't know how to say it, it's called layering the sound.
I layered two guitars on one guitar to make one phrase.
I used this technique.
By the way, which Les Paul is that?
This is a Gibson.
It's a Les Paul made by Gibson.
It's a family heirloom.
Family heirloom?
I'd say it's about family heirloom No. 3.
Heirloom No. 3?
It's like 3 or 4 or 5.
It's an heirloom, and I'd like to keep it as a guitarist as long as I can.
Yes, thank you very much.
Well, anyway, I'll keep it hot, straight, and straightforward.
Well, that guitar of Mr. Fukuda's is one thing, too
Well, I can't help but be too hot for every demo by Mr. Takahi!
So, of course, the momentum of the demo was exceeded, plus
Tsubaki sings it on stage, and the audience gets involved.
I had to concentrate all my energy on how much I could incorporate that image into the sound.
I had to put all my energy into it.
This stay free & stay tune can be a lot of fun at a live performance.
It's a very hot song, full of speed and full of drive.
Let's all shout it out together and get excited!
Yes, I hope you will get excited!
Please check it out...
Please watch it!
It's so much fun!
That was fun!
We both ate it up and watched it already!
It was so much fun!
There's so much behind the scenes that I didn't know.
That's true.
That's exactly what I was thinking when I was listening to the last two.
I was like... what does this mean when the word comes up?
And when you said that it was easy to play...
Oh, really? Like...
No, no...
No, no, no.
But you know, you guys are all so trusting of each other.
There's a mutual trust.
And we're able to make music with them.
We are happy to be able to make music together with them.
I was very happy to be able to work with them.
It was a wonderful atmosphere.
How was it?
Yes, it was.
The guitar recording was really cool.
I felt again that you take time and care in making a record like this.
I felt it again.
It made us feel like we want to showcase more of what we do.
I also felt that we want to showcase our music in this way.
I felt so much love.
I felt it!
We also want to sing with a lot of love and care
We want to sing with love and care.
Yes, I felt it.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory
Stay Free & Stay Tune Guitar Recording
We've been waiting for you!
Next up is Angulum Red Line Vocal Recording!
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki of Redline from Angulum's latest single.
Okay, let's go to the emu car.
First of all, I don't know if I'm allowed to be an idiot, so I'm just going to go home.
I'm going to go this far.
Angstrom Redline Vocal Recording
Angulum Red Line Vocal Recording
I want to go home a little bit
If you say you can make me feel like a boob star, then yes...
I wonder if it's okay to be an idiot
I'll be on the next bus, I just want to go home
OK, OK.
Here we go. Let's go to the next block.
Yes, yes.
Next block.
Is it true that you're in love with Aitaka?
In the middle of a work of art
Unwilling to be open and honest
Unconscious precaution
That's how you say it, and that's OK.
But you've got the right way to sing it, too.
OK, let's sing it
The way you sing is perfect.
Is it true that I missed you?
I've missed you too
I'm not being open and honest
unconscious precautions
Okay, so that's how it's going to be
I'm over my worries
I'm in a happy mood today
I was not being honest and excited, unconscious precautionary
I've been warming up to the idea of a happy today's coordinate.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's the feeling.
Let's give it another shot.
I'm not being honest and excited, but I'm unconsciously taking precautions.
I've been warming up to it, and I've been worrying about it, and I'm excited about today's coordinate.
Yeah, OK.
You can go to the next lap, or you can go to the second B. I'll go to the lap.
I'll go to the rap. Okay.
No need to make excuses that it's not appropriate I'm gonna sing for you
It's kind of cute.
I'll say something a little different.
It's kind of...
I thought you were cool and nice... and the game patty's a good problem to have.
Seth, I'm gonna sing for you.
What do you think?
ok... then I'm going to miss you...
I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say
I'm gonna say
I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I'm gonna say
I do I do I do love you, Teibow, to the end that you broke
Yeah, OK.
Okay, let's continue.
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Red Rae, this kiss is proof that you're ready
I do I do I do I'll only show it to you
Red Rae.
Isn't that nice? That's the feeling.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go one step further.
I do I do I do Love's taybo Beyond the breaking
Red Rae This kiss is proof of my resolve
I do I do I'll only show it to you
Red Rae.
OK.
Last one.
Oh yeah!
Let's really fall in love.
Let's do this.
The answer is "odenklap".
me
Serious love tax Clock
Oh yeah, Sasaki Yabe and I can say it here in a really cool way, right?
I'm sure you can say it very coolly here.
Yes, OK
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I saw your recording.
It was really cool.
That was cool.
So cool!
The song "Red Line" by Angulum is pretty dark in the intro.
The intro of the song is pretty dark.
but it's a song that builds and builds and builds and builds, so it's kind of like...
I think it's the depth of your bass sound, or the depth of your voice.
I thought his voice was really cool.
I thought it was really cool.
Your voice is really nice.
The way you pull it out and all the details are so nice.
It really made me go "hmmm".
I was saying "hmmm" as I watched it.
It was really cool.
I always watch your music videos, too.
I've played it over and over again.
Thank you so much!
I haven't seen it live yet, so I'm looking forward to seeing it live.
I've never seen it live yet, so I'm going to watch it live.
No, I've already finished it live.
That's how I feel about it.
I'm really looking forward to this song.
I hope you'll see it.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
I'm looking forward to seeing many more music videos and live performances.
That's all for the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki of Angulum Redline!
I'm always on your side.
With Moe Kokuryo, the god of Angulum
Beyons Amamori Kami's Shin Maeda is bringing you Apkami!
Next up is here!
Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest album
Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Please take a look at the vocal recording of Sakura Ishiyama!
Okay, let's start recording.
I'll start with the chorus.
First of all, we're going to start with the chorus, so please stand up with a gusto where the chorus is in order.
Yes, please.
Music
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
If only you were here
Here's Wonderful Forward
That's good.
One more shot just like that
Here's a wonder for word
It's a little bit low.
So you can make it a little brighter.
Yes, sir.
Then let's try one more.
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
If only you were here.
This is Wander for Earl
This is Wonder for Earl. Is that all?
Yes, sir.
When I think of you
This is Wonder for Art.
Let's go to number 2.
It's a dream.
Since we met, this world is beautiful, isn't it?
Life is fine
The feeling is really good.
And the rest, well...
It's a little hard to say it in such a high place.
It's hard to say it in high places.
You don't have to put too much effort into it.
I'm totally comfortable.
Let's go a little further.
I've found it.
It's a beautiful world, isn't it?
Life is beautiful.
Where were you looking?
I don't know where I was looking.
I thought if I sang without raising my hand, it would come out.
I don't know where you're looking.
It was fun. It's okay.
I'm glad.
You say you love me
And I say I love you
I don't say I love you
You say you love me
That's not exactly what I meant.
You say you
you in "you say you
I in I say I
Almost like you don't have to say it so firmly.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, just like that.
That's fine, isn't it? That's what I mean.
Let's do that, almost okay, but let's just give it one more shot.
Same feeling as when you're singing in the chorus.
It's the same feeling as when you sing "This world is..." It's like a brightness.
This kind of song with that feeling.
And the second you in the first shot where you say you love me, you don't have to say it so clearly. Yes, it is.
It's so clear that you can hear "You say you love me.
Yes. It's OK.
KAISEI.
You say you love me And I say I love you
Only you forever
Now let's do the "la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Yes, sir.
Only you forever
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Yes, yes, yes, I'll do it this way.
I think the head part is probably the hardest to get into.
Rah rah rah drown it one more time
drown it one more time
All you forever
Л preoccupation
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
That's all. Thank you very much. How was your recording of Sakura-chan's vocal?
Yes, well, Hiyomo and I talk with Sakura quite a bit, but it was really fun to see her working so hard on that part.
I thought she had a wonderful voice.
I'm also going to the Hello Project concert 3 of us with Juice Juice, so I'll be listening to Sakura-chan's voice.
I've been listening to Sakura-chan's voice at the Hello Project concert 3 of us with Juice Juice, and I think she's a girl who can hit the notes straight and true.
I was watching the video of the recording session, and I was really impressed by how well she got into the notes she was good at.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a few of them in the video, but I'm sure you'll be able to find a few of them in the video as well.
I love how many names you have!
I thought it was really fun to see the behind-the-scenes of recording sessions like this on the up-camera.
That's all for now.
That's all for JuiceJuice Wonderful World 2023 JUICEJuice Ver. Vocal recording of Sakura Ishiyama!
Ocha no oma! First album CHANNEL-1 is now on sale!
You can do it!
Kami Kokuri is Maeda
It's time to say goodbye to the up god that Maeda Kokoro has been presenting!
Yes, we've seen a lot of videos this time, but...
What did you think?
Well, I'm really looking forward to seeing the recording videos on Upgami.
Every time it is uploaded, I get excited to see who it is this time.
This time, I really enjoyed watching the videos of Rikako Sasaki and Sakura Ishiyama.
I'll tell you about the scene that left the biggest impression on me.
I remember the guitar lesson with Gaya during the recording session.
They looked like they were having fun.
The three of us were filming together.
I was shocked to see that it wasn't just about the guitar.
They looked like they were having a lot of fun.
What's more...
Yeah, the three of them looked like they were having fun.
They were so close.
They got along so well with each other.
I don't know what to say, but...
I thought they were so cute.
I said that, didn't I?
Yes, yes.
It's really just behind the scenes.
I'm glad I got to see that in Upgami.
So, upgami will be looking behind the scenes at the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
The parts you don't usually get to see.
I'll be showing you a lot of things you don't normally see.
I'll be introducing a lot of things you don't normally see, so please subscribe to the channel! So this time, upkami's partners are Anjelum's Kami Gore-o and
BEYONDZ: Shin Maeda of Kaomi Amamori.
In the next Takami, we'll talk about the recording of Wr.23 WAKE UP CALL and the new members of Tsubaki Factory,
lessons of the three new members of Tsubaki Factory will be shown.
Enjoy!